<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ACSBCP-Special Interest Group @ Bombay College of Pharmacy on ACSBCP-SIG</title>
    <link>https://bcpsig.club/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ACSBCP-Special Interest Group @ Bombay College of Pharmacy on ACSBCP-SIG</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bcpsig.club/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CompChem WG Meet #1</title>
      <link>https://bcpsig.club/posts/ccwg1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bcpsig.club/posts/ccwg1/</guid>
      <description>Greetings ! On Tuesday, October 10th 2023, ACSBCP-SIG held its introductory event that too its first ever Computational Chemistry Working Group Meet!
Darshan Barhate, T.Y. B.Pharm student, presented the paper titled &amp;lsquo;Genes mirroring geography within Europe&amp;rsquo; by Novembre et.al. Darshan presented how genetic and geographical variation are interrelated and what are the possible implications of these findings for disease research &amp;amp; ancestral locations of individuals.
Manas Mahale , also a T.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BCPSIG Committee &#39;24</title>
      <link>https://bcpsig.club/posts/team/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bcpsig.club/posts/team/</guid>
      <description>Greetings, BCPSIG is elated to announce the 2023-2024 BCPSIG Committee members.
President Vinit Chaudhari Vice President Abhishek Karulkar Secretary Ayushi Verma Events Coordinator Mehek Joshi Events Member Shanmathi R K Outreach Coordinator Suraj Shivaji Lotale Outreach Member Karan Gupta Yogesh Khairnar Treasurer Nidhi Sunil Vaidya Membership Coordinator Tisha Uge Working Group Coordinator Darshan Ramkrishna Barhate Public Relations Coordinator Satyam Thakur Public Relations Member Siya Malvi Rukmin Patwardhan </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SIG002</title>
      <link>https://bcpsig.club/posts/sig002/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bcpsig.club/posts/sig002/</guid>
      <description>Greetings ! Python programming has become an indispensable tool in various fields, including computational chemistry. Manas Mahale, representing the Computational Chemistry Working Group of the Special Interest Group at Bombay College of Pharmacy, recently delivered an insightful presentation titled
&amp;ldquo;Introduction to Python Programming&amp;rdquo;.
In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll provide a summary of the key takeaways from this presentation, making it accessible to those who missed it. We will also share the link to the recorded presentation and the presentation slides.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SIG001</title>
      <link>https://bcpsig.club/posts/sig001/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bcpsig.club/posts/sig001/</guid>
      <description>Greetings ! It is our great pleasure to report the inaugural session of the Special Interst Group at BCP was successfully conducted. This post will briefly touch upon the highlights of the event.
Introduction to SIG @ BCP SIG, a novelty at BCP was introduced with all its facets including the Working Groups of SIG which are collaborative and nurturing collective of people interested in same / similar niche research areas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Beginning</title>
      <link>https://bcpsig.club/posts/newbeginning/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bcpsig.club/posts/newbeginning/</guid>
      <description>Greetings ! Welcome to the Special Interest Group at Bombay College of Pharmacy (BCPSIG). We are a dynamic and innovative community of aspiring pharmaceutical researchers dedicated to pushing the boundaries of scientific discovery in the world of pharmaceuticals.
Our Mission: Our mission is to inspire, educate, and collaborate in the field of pharmaceutical research. We provide a platform for students and researchers to come together, share knowledge, and engage in cutting-edge research projects.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
